<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<flinks>
<item>
<id>0</id>
<title>Al Ameen 24-hour hotline</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/alameen.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.alameen.ae/en/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Al Ameen service was launched in September 2003. Its communication between community members and administration with the security to keep abreast developments in the Dubai city.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>1</id>
<title>Awqaf and Minors Affairs Foundation</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/awqaf.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.amaf.gov.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>Awqaf and Minors Affairs Foundation undertakes guardianship of Awqaf in terms of investments and legal protection...</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>2</id>
<title>Community Development Authority</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/cda.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.cda.gov.ae/en/Pages/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>CDA is established to create and provide social services and protection net for all the people of Dubai and to continuously elevate social standards through an integrated system of policies...</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>3</id>
<title>Department of Economic Development</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/departmentofeconomy.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaided.gov.ae/english/pages/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>The Department of Economic Development was established with the objective to organise, regulate and boost trade and industry within the Emirate of Dubai.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>4</id>
<title>Department of Finance</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_1.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dof.gov.ae/en-us/pages/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>The vision of the Dubai Department of Finance is based on the sound management of public finance to achieve balance between the emirate’s strategic economic objectives.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>5</id>
<title>Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/tourism.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaitourism.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>The website of the Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM) in Dubai provides valuable information about the emirate, DTCM newsletter, tourism, etc...</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>6</id>
<title>Dubai Airport Free Zone</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dfz_1.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dafz.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Airport Free Zone Authority was established in 1996 as part of the Dubai Strategic Plan. It occupies a strategic position in the vicinity of Dubai International Airport.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>7</id>
<title>Dubai Cares</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dubaicares_E.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaicares.ae/en</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Cares was launched by Dubai’s Ruler to help countries achieve the UN Millennium Development Goal by making primary education available to every child by 2015.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>8</id>
<title>Dubai Chamber</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dubaichamber.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaichamber.com/</websiteurl>
<details>Established in 1965, the Chamber has been at the centre of Dubai’s commercial activities for over 35 years and played a big role in supporting the national economy of the country .</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>9</id>
<title>Dubai City Guide</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dubaicityguide.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaicityguide.com/site/main/index.asp</websiteurl>
<details>The Dubai City Guide engages web surfers in a short tour on famous landmarks in Dubai including shopping centers, entertainment venues, hotels, etc..</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>10</id>
<title>Dubai Civil Aviation Authority 	</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_10.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dcaa.gov.ae/Default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Civil Aviation Authority undertakes development of Air Transport Industry in the Emirate of Dubai and oversees all aviation related activities including management…</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>11</id>
<title>Dubai Civil Defence 	</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_6.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dcd.gov.ae/eng/index.php</websiteurl>
<details>The website of Dubai Civil Defence (DCD) provides scientific information, accurate news and increase preventive awareness among public, business community and different government sectors.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>12</id>
<title>Dubai Corporation for Ambulance Service</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_9.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.ambulance.gov.ae/arabic/Pages/home.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>The Corporation provides ambulance services in Dubai by taking part in the comprehensive strategic plans related to ambulance services in Dubai, preparing, developing and…</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>13</id>
<title>Dubai Courts 	</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_21.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaicourts.gov.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>The main purpose of Dubai Courts is to achieve justice through accuracy and promptness in settlement, disposition and execution of judgments and attestation of written instruments.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>14</id>
<title>Dubai Customs</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dubaicustoms.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dxbcustoms.gov.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Customs, one of the leading customs administrations in the region, offers all information and services provided by Dubai Customs.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>15</id>
<title>Dubai Drydocks</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/drydocks.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.drydocks.gov.ae/en/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Drydocks World is the largest facility in the Middle East and is the flagship company of Dubai World's subsidiary, Drydocks World.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>16</id>
<title>Dubai e-Government Department</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_2.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.deg.gov.ae/en/pages/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai e-Government is a modern concept of Dubai Government. It stands on the best utilization of information technology to provide the government’s services for public…</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>17</id>
<title>Dubai Electricity and Water Authority</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dewa.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>DEWA was formed to provide the people of Dubai with an adequate supply of electricity and water.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>18</id>
<title>Dubai Export Development Corporation</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_11.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dedc.gov.ae/en/Pages/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Export Development Corporation aims to create suitable environment for export activities, increase competiveness, provide value-added services…</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>19</id>
<title>Dubai Golf</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dubaigolf.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaigolf.com/</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Golf is the first grass course in the region. Through its mix of fine-dining restaurants, and swimming, fitness and tennis facilities, it is an all-encompassing leisure hub.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>20</id>
<title>Dubai Government Human Resources Department</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_17.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dghr.gov.ae/ar/Pages/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Government Human Resources Department is aspired to build a distinguished and pioneer national model, with international standards…</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>21</id>
<title>Dubai Government Workshop</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_18.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dgw.gov.ae/EN/Home.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Government Workshop is a leading institution in transport services and maintenance of vehicles, machineries and equipments. 	</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>22</id>
<title>Dubai Health Authority</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_26.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>ttp://www.dha.gov.ae/En/pages/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>To develop a world-class integrated health system in the Emirate of Dubai by developing and implementing plans, policies and legislations that promotes excellence in private and public medical facilities.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>23</id>
<title>Dubai International</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dubai-internationa.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaiairport.com/en/Pages/home.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai International includes a virtual tour at Dubai International Airport, a list of restaurants and cafes, airlines and the flying programmes, in addition to several other services.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>24</id>
<title>Dubai International Financial Centre</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/difc.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.difc.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>DIFC is the onshore finance and business hub connecting the region to the world. It promotes state of the art infrastructure to our stakeholders.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>25</id>
<title>Dubai International Holy Quran Award</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/holyquranaward.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.quran.gov.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>DIHQA was founded in 1997 as per the directives of UAE Vice President, Prime Minister and Ruler of Dubai His Highness Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>26</id>
<title>Dubai Internet City</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dic.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaiinternetcity.com/</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Internet City provides a knowledge economy ecosystem that is designed to support the business development of information and communications technology (ICT) companies.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>27</id>
<title>Dubai Knowledge Village</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dkv.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.kv.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Knowledge Village offers a state-of-the-art campus dedicated to learning excellence.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>28</id>
<title>Dubai Media City</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dmc-eng.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaimediacity.com/</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Media City is the place where activities publishing, music, film, leisure, entertainment, broadcasting, media and marketing services and information agencies thrive.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>29</id>
<title>Dubai Media Incorporated (DMI)</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_13.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dmi.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>DMI operates through values of innovation, quality and modernization and in compliance with Dubai’s strategic objectives. 	</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>30</id>
<title>Dubai Municipality</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dubaimunicipality.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://login.dm.gov.ae/wps/portal/HomeEn</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Municipality, working to plan, design, build and manage the municipal services through the appropriate investment in our human and other resources.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>31</id>
<title>Dubai Police</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dubaipolice.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaipolice.gov.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>The Dubai Police site includes a list of police stations in Dubai and a variety of web-based services. It also displays a variety of services provided by Dubai Police.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>32</id>
<title>Dubai Press Club</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dpc.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dpc.org.ae/Portal/en/home.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Press Club is a well- established forum for journalists and media professionals to debate discuss and deliberate upon issues that are relevant to daily life.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>33</id>
<title>Dubai Public Prosecution</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_14.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dxbpp.gov.ae/Eservices.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Public Prosecution (DPP) aims to make the community safer by protecting the legal rights and freedoms of the community working with their partners to bring about fair and more secure society. 	</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>34</id>
<title>Dubai School of Government</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_22.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dsg.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>ubai School of Government is a research tank and education institute specialized in public policies. The School targets enhancement of government institutions’ competencies to adopt effective public policies in the UAE and the region.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>35</id>
<title>Dubai Shopping Festival</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dsf.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaievents.ae/en</websiteurl>
<details>The site provides you with information on Dubai Shopping Festival, the most splendid annual family event . It displays centers and places participating in the festival etc.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>36</id>
<title>Dubai Sports Council</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_25.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaisportscouncil.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>The Council is involved in developing sports in the emirate of Dubai and creating a comprehensive athletic environment that allows youth to polish their athletic talents…</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>37</id>
<title>Dubai Statistics Center</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_24.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dsc.gov.ae/en/pages/home.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Statistics Center is the official source of statistical data in the Emirate of Dubai. The Center undertakes statistical activities, carrying out the general census of population, and the count of housing and establishments.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>38</id>
<title>Dubai Summer Surprises</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dss.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaievents.ae/en</websiteurl>
<details>The site contains statistics for DSS since its inception, details of activities and events planned for summer in Dubai, and other information about Dubai.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>39</id>
<title>Dubai Trade</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_3.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaitrade.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>By an initiative from several distinguished basic-services establishments in Dubai, Dubai trade was formed to develop and assist commercial and logistic operations in the emirate.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>40</id>
<title>Dubai World Cup</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/dubaiworldcup.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://dubairacingclub.com/dubai-world-cup</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai World Cup contains information about the world's top horseracing challenges. It gives information about racing dates, bookings, and other horseracing information.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>41</id>
<title>Emirates Airline</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/emirates.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.emirates.com/ae/english/</websiteurl>
<details>The official site of Dubai's award-winning Emirates Airline contains information about the company’s services, including destinations, booking, seasonal offers etc.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>42</id>
<title>Emirates Holidays</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/emirates-holiday.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.emirates-holidays.com/english/</websiteurl>
<details>Emirates Holidays includes the history of the company and its services and its travel destinations all over the world. Other services can also be found on this useful site.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>43</id>
<title>Financial Audit Department 	</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_20.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://fad.gov.ae/en/index.html</websiteurl>
<details>Financial Audit Department is the highest auditing authority in Dubai. Its competencies includes all government departments, public corporations…</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>44</id>
<title>General Directorate of Residency and Foreigners Affairs-Dubai</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_12.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://dnrd.ae/en/Pages/Home.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>he General Directorate of Residency and Foreigners Affairs aims to facilitate and speed up procedures and reduce congestion through implementation of integrated electronic systems that increase productivity dramatically over the past few years..</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>45</id>
<title>Godolphin</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/godolphic_big.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.godolphin.com/</websiteurl>
<details>Godolphin, the Maktoum family's private horseracing stable, was named in honour of the Godolphin Arabian, who came from the desert to become one of the three founding stallions of the modern thoroughbred.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>46</id>
<title>Hamdan Bin Mohammed e-University</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/hamdan-university.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.hbmeu.ac.ae/en/home/</websiteurl>
<details>The University offers high quality programmes using a virtual learning environment, while in support of lifelong learning and economic development in the Arab World.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>47</id>
<title>Islamic Affairs and Charitable Activities</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_7.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.iacad.gov.ae/en/Pages/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>The prime objective of the Islamic affairs and Charitable Activities is to promote Islamic culture and develop religious awareness in the region.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>48</id>
<title>Jebel Ali Free Zone</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/jafza.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.jafza.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>Jebel Ali Free Zone is one of the world’s largest and the fastest growing free zones in the world. The site also contains information about JAFZA's facilities, incentives and rules and regulations.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>49</id>
<title>Jumeirah Hotels and Resorts Worldwide</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/jumeirah.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.jumeirah.com/</websiteurl>
<details>The site includes information about the Jumeirah Group, a list of its hotels and prices, booking online etc. The site is in four languages Arabic, English, French and Russian.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>50</id>
<title>Knowledge and Human Development Authority (KHDA)</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_19.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.khda.gov.ae/en/home.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>KHDA is a regulatory authority responsible for the growth, direction and quality of education and learning in Dubai in compliance with highest international standards and according to work-market expectations. 	</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>51</id>
<title>Land Department</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_16.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubailand.gov.ae/EngDefault.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>Land Department carries out all matters related to documentation and authentication of real-estate transactions in addition to approving all regulations related to organizing real-estate markets. 	</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>52</id>
<title>Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Foundation</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/AlMaktoumE.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.mbrfoundation.ae/English/Pages/Default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>This foundation is tasked with devising sustainable, home-grown solutions to regional challenges, through increasing the dissemination of knowledge throughout the region.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>53</id>
<title>Nakheel</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/nakheel.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.nakheel.com/en/</websiteurl>
<details>The site gives information about Nakheel, one of the world’s biggest real estate companies. It also focuses on Dubai’s 3 man-made palm-shaped islands, building icons that embody innovation and progress.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>54</id>
<title>Noor Dubai</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/noor_dubaiE.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.noor-dubai.com/</websiteurl>
<details>Noor Dubai started as an international charitable initiative launched by Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid on September 3, 2008 for the prevention and treatment of blindness and low vision.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>55</id>
<title>The Protocol Department of Dubai 	</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_23.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://protocol.dubai.ae/EN/Pages/default.aspx</websiteurl>
<details>The Protocol Department of Dubai is responsible for managing and organizing all protocols for His Highness Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>56</id>
<title>Roads and Transport Authority (RTA)</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_15.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.rta.ae/wpsv5/wps/portal/rta/home/!ut/p/c5/04_SB8K8xLLM9MSSzPy8xBz9CP0os3gfd9cAfwM3M0N_PydnA0_TEFNjR0NPAyAAykeaxRvgAI4GBHSHg-wD6TcN9gmz8LZwMXA2CvMzNDIxhpoAk8dpvp9Hfm6qfnBikX5BboRBlomjIgCSRM5E/dl3/d3/L0lHSkovd0RNQU5rQUVnQSEhL1lCZncvZW4!/?locale.switch=true</websiteurl>
<details>RTA is responsible for planning, managing and executing transportation and roads projects in the emirate of Dubai.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>57</id>
<title>Sheikh Hamdan bin Rashid Al Maktoum Award for Medical Sciences</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/SHmdan-Bin-Rashid-Prize.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.hmaward.org.ae/site/</websiteurl>
<details>Information about the award for exceptional achievements in the field of medicine.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>58</id>
<title>Tejari</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/tejari.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.tejari.com/cms/uae</websiteurl>
<details>Tejari is the leading B2B online marketplace in the emerging markets. Tejari enables buyers and sellers to transact and share information via a secured Internet.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>59</id>
<title>The Dubai Culture and Arts Authority (Dubai Culture)</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/logo_4.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.dubaiculture.ae/en</websiteurl>
<details>Dubai Culture aims at establishing Dubai as one of the most vibrant, cosmopolitan and diversified cities in the world in terms of cultures and arts, and as a hub where East... West. Dubai Culture also encourages</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>60</id>
<title>The Prime Minister's website</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/uaepm.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://uaepm.ae/English/Pages/default.aspx?Mobile=0</websiteurl>
<details>An official source of information for the Prime Minister, and a communication platform connecting the UAE PM, citizens and foreign and local media.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>61</id>
<title>Young Arab Leaders</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/LeaderShip.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.yaleaders.org/en/</websiteurl>
<details>Young Arab Leaders, a non-profit organisation, was founded at the 2004 World Economic Forum in Jordan. The organisation has 464 members in nine countries.</details>
</item>
<item>
<id>62</id>
<title>Zayed International Prize for the Environment</title>
<thumbnail>http://www.dewa.gov.ae/images/smartgov/icons/zayedintl.jpg</thumbnail>
<largeimage />
<websiteurl>http://www.zayedprize.org.ae/</websiteurl>
<details>The Zayed International Prize for the Environment recognises pioneers in the field of environment and sustainable development.</details>
</item>
</flinks>